{
    "user_name": "fra",
    "session_complete_time": "2018-12-04 19:55:23.852604",
    "session_pk": 11,
    "session_size": 6,
    "block_size": 6,
    "policy_id": 1,
    "block_data": [
        {
            "block_id": 46,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 273,
                    "question_pk": 959,
                    "question": "We had been trying for three hours and now all of a sudden this little boy was standing in front of me, rubbing his eyes.",
                    "chunk": "We had been trying for three hours ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Wir hatten es drei Stunden lang versucht",
                    "answer": "We have been trying for three hours ",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 274,
                    "question_pk": 787,
                    "question": "I felt very attached to the brave pair and found it quite hard to leave them.",
                    "chunk": "it quite hard to leave them",
                    "chunk_translation": "es ist ziemlich schwer, sie zu verlassen",
                    "answer": "it quite hard to leave them",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 275,
                    "question_pk": 191,
                    "question": "Before the operation, I posted a video of him dancing on the Ed Sullivan Show, and thought, In one year, I'll be doing this.",
                    "chunk": "of him dancing on the Ed Sullivan Show",
                    "chunk_translation": "von ihm tanzen auf der Ed Sullivan Show",
                    "answer": "of him dancing on the Ed Sullivan Show",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 276,
                    "question_pk": 166,
                    "question": "I was really upset: why had I been through so many operations?",
                    "chunk": "why had I been through so many operations",
                    "chunk_translation": "Warum hatte ich so viele Operationen durchgemacht?",
                    "answer": "why had I been through so many operations ",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 277,
                    "question_pk": 911,
                    "question": "We moved the safe away from the wall; behind it we found some papers and a manual, which had several codes written on it.",
                    "chunk": "some papers and a manual",
                    "chunk_translation": "einige Papiere und ein Handbuch",
                    "answer": "some papers and a manual",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 278,
                    "question_pk": 389,
                    "question": "I had a voicemail from one of the ski instructors saying: Hey, just to let you know it's a really high avalanche risk today, there have been three people buried in avalanches in different areas already, so just be very careful.",
                    "chunk": "the ski instructors ",
                    "chunk_translation": "die Skilehrer",
                    "answer": "the ski instructors",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 47,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 279,
                    "question_pk": 1227,
                    "question": "Having created something that changed and improved my own life, and having benefited from others' open-source work, I wanted to share our work so other people could use it.",
                    "chunk": "so other people could use it",
                    "chunk_translation": "damit andere Leute es benutzen k\u00f6nnten",
                    "answer": "so other people could use it",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 280,
                    "question_pk": 398,
                    "question": "Skiing is still my biggest passion, but I don't take risks any more.",
                    "chunk": "don't take risks any more",
                    "chunk_translation": "gehe kein Risiko mehr ein",
                    "answer": "don't take risks any more",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 281,
                    "question_pk": 1244,
                    "question": "Many of us have no medical or engineering training and we work on improvements in the evening or at the weekend, for free.",
                    "chunk": "no medical or engineering training ",
                    "chunk_translation": "kein medizinisches oder technisches Training",
                    "answer": "no medical or engineering training",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 282,
                    "question_pk": 14,
                    "question": "I'd have preferred a really fast one that went upside down.",
                    "chunk": "a really fast one ",
                    "chunk_translation": "ein wirklich schneller",
                    "answer": "a really fast one",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 283,
                    "question_pk": 470,
                    "question": "Sebastian began to cry: he could see I was in pain.",
                    "chunk": "I was in pain",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich hatte Schmerzen",
                    "answer": "I was in pain",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 284,
                    "question_pk": 314,
                    "question": "I was screaming for help, but trying not to use up too much oxygen.",
                    "chunk": "trying not to use up too much oxygen",
                    "chunk_translation": "versuchen, nicht zu viel Sauerstoff zu verbrauchen",
                    "answer": "tried not to use up too much oxygen",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 48,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 285,
                    "question_pk": 1225,
                    "question": "Having created something that changed and improved my own life, and having benefited from others' open-source work, I wanted to share our work so other people could use it.",
                    "chunk": "other people could use it",
                    "chunk_translation": "andere Leute k\u00f6nnten es benutzen",
                    "answer": "other people could use it",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 286,
                    "question_pk": 613,
                    "question": "I'd copy my friend's work; he knew something was wrong, so let me.",
                    "chunk": "he knew something was wrong",
                    "chunk_translation": "Er wusste, dass etwas nicht stimmte",
                    "answer": "he knew something was wrong",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 287,
                    "question_pk": 302,
                    "question": "It was like trying to breathe through a heavy cloth.",
                    "chunk": "breathe through a heavy cloth",
                    "chunk_translation": "durch ein schweres Tuch atmen",
                    "answer": "breathe through a heavy cloth",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 288,
                    "question_pk": 22,
                    "question": "I'd also had a glass of Famous Grouse whisky to give me a bit of courage.",
                    "chunk": "give me a bit of courage",
                    "chunk_translation": "gib mir ein bisschen Mut",
                    "answer": "give me a bit of courage",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 289,
                    "question_pk": 643,
                    "question": "I had passed all my practical exams, preparing for them by learning by heart and intently watching people who were good at their job.",
                    "chunk": "people who were good at their job",
                    "chunk_translation": "Menschen, die gut in ihrem Job waren",
                    "answer": "people who were good at their job",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 290,
                    "question_pk": 648,
                    "question": "The examining doctor wanted an explanation.",
                    "chunk": "The examining doctor ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Der untersuchende Arzt",
                    "answer": "The examining doctor",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 49,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 291,
                    "question_pk": 974,
                    "question": "He had a cuddle with his tearful mother, a checkup from the doctor, and then went for a shower  he was sweaty and his clothes were wet from breathing in that tiny space for so long.",
                    "chunk": "that tiny space ",
                    "chunk_translation": "dieser winzige Raum",
                    "answer": "that tiny space",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 292,
                    "question_pk": 1173,
                    "question": "From there, it was a small step to build a webpage so I could add a snooze button to press after taking action.",
                    "chunk": "press after taking action",
                    "chunk_translation": "Dr\u00fccken Sie nach der Aktion",
                    "answer": "press after action taken",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 293,
                    "question_pk": 1180,
                    "question": "Scott and I also created an algorithm that forecasted when my blood sugar was likely to become low or too high, sending alerts to my phone or smartwatch.",
                    "chunk": "my blood sugar ",
                    "chunk_translation": "mein Blutzucker",
                    "answer": "my blood sugar",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 294,
                    "question_pk": 1226,
                    "question": "Having created something that changed and improved my own life, and having benefited from others' open-source work, I wanted to share our work so other people could use it.",
                    "chunk": "that changed and improved my own life",
                    "chunk_translation": "Das hat mein eigenes Leben ver\u00e4ndert und verbessert",
                    "answer": "that changed and improved my own life",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 295,
                    "question_pk": 233,
                    "question": "Well, that's because I'm dancing on one leg!",
                    "chunk": "dancing on one leg",
                    "chunk_translation": "auf einem Bein tanzen",
                    "answer": "dancing on one leg",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 296,
                    "question_pk": 759,
                    "question": "Becky had read that hypothermia is a common cause of death in newborn lambs, so I wrapped it in my jacket.",
                    "chunk": "a common cause ",
                    "chunk_translation": "eine gemeinsame Ursache",
                    "answer": "a common cause",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 50,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 297,
                    "question_pk": 534,
                    "question": "My first birth took two and a half days  this one was over and done with in two and a half hours.",
                    "chunk": "My first birth ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Meine erste Geburt",
                    "answer": "My first birth",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 298,
                    "question_pk": 949,
                    "question": "It was dangerous, but I was confident that we could get him out.",
                    "chunk": "we could get him out",
                    "chunk_translation": "wir k\u00f6nnten ihn rausholen",
                    "answer": "we could get him out",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 299,
                    "question_pk": 272,
                    "question": "I'm now auditioning for principal Broadway roles, and was nominated for outstanding actor in a musical at the Drama Desk awards this year.",
                    "chunk": "for principal Broadway roles",
                    "chunk_translation": "f\u00fcr Haupt Broadway Rollen",
                    "answer": "for Broadway principal role",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 300,
                    "question_pk": 124,
                    "question": "I'm taking it easy now, so I find challenges to spice things up.",
                    "chunk": "taking it easy now",
                    "chunk_translation": "es jetzt leicht machen",
                    "answer": "taking it easy now",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 301,
                    "question_pk": 954,
                    "question": "Then, just as we started to make the first cut, my colleague punched in the correct code.",
                    "chunk": "in the correct code",
                    "chunk_translation": "im richtigen Code",
                    "answer": "in the correct code",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 302,
                    "question_pk": 284,
                    "question": "As an experienced skier, I was excited rather than concerned.",
                    "chunk": "excited rather than concerned",
                    "chunk_translation": "eher aufgeregt als besorgt",
                    "answer": "rather excited than concerned",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 51,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 303,
                    "question_pk": 579,
                    "question": "Johnny was the funny, good-looking guy whom everyone loved; Josh was the boy inside who wanted to learn, but couldn't.",
                    "chunk": "was the funny, good-looking guy whom everyone loved",
                    "chunk_translation": "war der lustige, gut aussehende Kerl, den alle liebten",
                    "answer": "was the funny good-looking guy whom everyone loved",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 304,
                    "question_pk": 1115,
                    "question": "Some people fall from 20ft and die, so to fall from 500ft and walk away without serious injuries is mind-boggling.",
                    "chunk": "without serious injuries ",
                    "chunk_translation": "ohne ernsthafte Verletzungen",
                    "answer": "without serious injuries",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 305,
                    "question_pk": 1066,
                    "question": "There were huge abrasions on my right leg from where the metal cables had zipped through my skin  I don't know how they didn't cut my legs off.",
                    "chunk": "didn't cut my legs off",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich habe mir die Beine nicht abgeschnitten",
                    "answer": "didn't cut off my legs",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 306,
                    "question_pk": 464,
                    "question": "We decided to pull up outside a medical centre that, luckily, happened to be en route.",
                    "chunk": "to be en route",
                    "chunk_translation": "sein und routen",
                    "answer": "to be en route",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 307,
                    "question_pk": 604,
                    "question": "When I had to write anything down, I guessed, forming what I hoped were the right words.",
                    "chunk": "I had to write anything down",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich musste etwas notieren",
                    "answer": "I had to write anything down",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 308,
                    "question_pk": 423,
                    "question": "My husband Richard and I stayed at home until my contractions were five minutes apart  we didn't realise that, because this was my second birth, we weren't supposed to wait.",
                    "chunk": "this was my second birth",
                    "chunk_translation": "Das war meine zweite Geburt",
                    "answer": "this was my second birth",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}